http://www.palmspringsairmuseum.org/privacy-policy/

Home›Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. We may collect personally identifiable information when you visit our site. We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you visited. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to anyone.
Security Policy
Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.
Returns
Returns must be made within 15 days of receipt. All refunds will be provided as a credit to the credit card used at the time of purchase within five (5) business days upon receipt of the returned merchandise. All sales final on sale merchandise. Please contact us with question about returns or exchanges. Call 760-778-6262. All returns must be shipped back to 745 N. Gene Autry Trail
Palm Springs, CA 92262
Shipping
Please be assured that your items will ship out within three days of purchase. Unless it’s a special order. We determine the most efficient shipping carrier for your order. The carriers that may be used are: United Parcel Service (UPS). Sorry but we cannot ship to P.O.Boxes/International addresses.
Please Note
All orders will be applied appropriate state sale tax.
Top
